Guide to the American Dance Festival Company and Biographical Reference Collection, 1934-2003
American Dance Festival Archives
- Subject Files, 1934-2003
  - Mordine & Company, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Morris, Mark Morris Dance Group, 2000 (Box 5)
  - Morris, Margaret, 1954 (Box 5)
  - Moulton, Charles, 1982 (Box 5)
  - Muller, Jennifer, 1974 (Box 5)
  - Multigravitational Experiment Group, 1974-1975 (Box 5)
  - Munson, Richard, 1982 (Box 5)
  - Murphy, Seamus Murphy Dance Company, 1970 (Box 5)
  - Musard, Yves, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Musard, Yves, undated (Box 5)
  - Myers, Martha, 1973 (Box 5)
  - Myers, Martha, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Myers, Martha, 2000 (Box 5)
  - Nagrin, Daniel, 1957-1958 (Box 5)
  - Nagrin, Daniel, 1966 (Box 5)
  - Nagrin, Daniel, 1970-1972 (Box 5)
  - Nagrin, Daniel, 1974 (Box 5)
  - Nagrin, Daniel, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - Najan, Nala, 1975 (Box 5)
  - Nash, Joe, undated (Box 5)
  - National Theatre of the Deaf, 1968 (Box 5)
  - Neo Classic Dance Company, circa 1978 (Box 5)
  - Neta Dance Company, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Netherlands Dance Theater, circa 1979 (Box 5)
  - Neuhaus, Max, 1964 (Box 5)
  - New Dance Group, undated (Box 5)
  - New England Chamber Opera Group, 1974 (Box 5)
  - New Haven Ballet, 1970 (Box 5)
  - Newman, Rosalind Newman and Dancers, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Newman, Rosalind Newman and Dancers, 1978 (Box 5)
  - New York City Ballet, 1971 (Box 5)
  - Next Ice Age, 1997-1999 (Box 5)
  - Next Move Theatre Company, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Nicholas Brothers, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Nicholas, Harold, 2000 (Box 5)
  - Nicholas, The Nicholas Sisters, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Nicks, Walter, undated (Box 5)
  - Nikolais, Alwin, circa 1955 (Box 5)
  - Nikolais, Alwin, 1956-1957 (Box 5)
  - Nikolais, Alwin Nikolais Dance Company, 1966 (Box 5)
  - Nikolais, Alwin Nikolais Dance Theatre, 1970 (Box 5)
  - Nikolais Dance Theatre, 1973-1974 (Box 5)
  - Nikolais Dance Theatre, 1976-1977 (Box 5)
  - Nikolais Dance Theatre, circa 1982 (Box 5)
  - Nikolais, Alwin, 1984-1991 (Box 5)
  - Nikolais, Alwin, 1993 (Box 5)
  - Nikolais, Alwin Nikolais and Murray Louis, 1999 (Box 5)
  - Nirenska, Pola, undated (Box 5)
  - North Carolina Dance Theater, undated (Box 5)
  - Noyes School of Rhythm, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Nucleodanza, undated (Box 5)
  - Nuevo Teatro de Danza, 1955 (Box 5)
  - Nurock, Kirk Nurock and Natural Sound, 1975-1976 (Box 5)
  - Nye, Libby, 1965 (Box 5)
  - Oberlin Dance Collective, 1978 (Box 6)
  - ODC, 1990-1997 (Box 6)
  - O'Hara, Shane, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Ontological-Hysteric Theatre, 1974 (Box 6)
  - Open Eye, The, 1974-1975 (Box 6)
  - Paper Bag Players, 1962 (Box 6)
  - Parsons Dance Company, 1997-1998 (Box 6)
  - Parsons, David, 1988-1992 (Box 6)
  - Pearson, Sara and Jerry, 1974 (Box 6)
  - Pearson, Sara, 1987-1988 (Box 6)
  - Pennison, Marleen Pennison and Dancers, 1980-1984 (Box 6)
  - Pennsylvania Ballet Company, 1974 (Box 6)
  - Pepatian, 1998 (Box 6)
  - Perez, Rudy, 1970-1974 (Box 6)
  - Rudy Perez Dance Theatre, 1978 (Box 6)
  - Perez, Rudy Perez Dance Theater, undated (Box 6)
  - Performance Group, 1974-1975 (Box 6)
  - Philadanco, 1979 (Box 6)
  - Philadanco, 1988-1997 (Box 6)
  - Philadanco, 1988 (Box 6)
  - Philippine Dance Company, 1974 (Box 6)
  - Pierce, Elizabeth Thames (Accompanist/Composer), 1956 (Box 6)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, 1973-1977 (Box 6)
  - Pilobolus, 1983-1986 (Box 6)
  - Pilobolus, 1993 (Box 6)
  - Pilobolus, 1998-1999 (Box 6)
  - Pilobolus, 2000 (Box 6)
  - Pilobolus, undated (Box 6)
  - Pilobolus Dance Theatre, undated (Box 6)
  - Pinto, Inbal, 2001 (Box 6)
  - Pomare, Eleo Pomare Dance Company, circa 1967 (Box 6)
  - Pomare, Eleo, Dance Company, 1974 (Box 6)
  - Pope, Heidi, Dance Studio, 1966 (Box 6)
  - Posin, Kathryn Posin Dance Company, 1974-1975 (Box 6)
  - Posin, Kathryn, undated (Box 6)
  - Preljocaj, Le Ballet Preljocaj, undated (Box 6)
  - Primous Fountain, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Primus, Pearl, circa 1946-1947 (Box 6)
  - Primus, Pearl and Her Company, circa 1951-1957 (Box 6)
  - Primus, Pearl, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Primus, Pearl, undated (Box 6)
  - Primus, Pearl, 1944 (Box 6)
  - Primus, Pearl and Valerie Bettis, 1944 (Box 6)
  - Primus, Pearl, 1943 (Box 6)
  - Primus, Pearl, 1943 (Box 6)
  - Proposition, The, 1975 (Box 6)
  - Public Opera Theatre Company, 1974 (Box 6)
  - Quitzow, Diane and Vol, 1958 (Box 6)
  - Qwindo's Window, 1974 (Box 6)
  - Raducanu, Miriam, 1973 (Box 6)
  - Rainer, Yvonne, circa 1965 (Box 6)
  - Rainer, Yvonne Rainer and the Grand Union, 1971 (Box 6)
  - Ravon, Ruth, 1960 (Box 6)
  - Redlich, Don, circa 1970-1979 (Box 6)
  - Redlich, Don Redlich Dance Company, circa 1975 (Box 6)
  - Redlich, Don Redlich Dance Company, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Redlich, Don, undated (Box 6)
  - Redlich, Don, undated (Box 6)
  - Redlich, Don, undated (Box 6)
  - Redlich, Don, undated (Box 6)
  - Redlich, Don, undated (Box 6)
  - Reinhart, Charles, circa 1975 (Box 6)
  - Reinhart, Charles, 1977 (Box 6)
  - Reinhart, Charles, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Reinhart, Charles and Stephanie, 2000 (Box 6)
  - Reka and Company, 1979 (Box 6)
  - Repertory Dance Theatre, 1978 (Box 6)
  - Richardson, Larry, and Dance Company, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Ridiculous Theatrical Company, 1974-1975 (Box 6)
  - Ririe Woodbury Dance Company, 1978 (Box 6)
  - Robinson, Cleo Parker Robinson Dance, 1995 (Box 6)
  - Robinson, Cleo Parker Robinson Dance, 1998 (Box 6)
  - Rogers, Helen Priest, circa 1967 (Box 6)
  - Rogers, Rod Rogers Dance Co, 1972-1975 (Box 6)
  - Rogoff, Tamar, 1987-1989 (Box 6)
  - Roope, Clover, circa 1967 (Box 6)
  - Rosenberg, Douglas, undated (Box 6)
  - Ross, Bertram, 1967 (Box 6)
  - Roxanne Dance Foundation, 1974 (Box 6)
  - Rush Dance Company, 1978 (Box 6)
  - Ryder, Mark, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Saint Paul Chamber Orchestra, 1974 (Box 6)
  - Paul Sanasardo Dance Company, 1974, 1976 (Box 7)
  - Sanders, Dora, 1964 (Box 7)
  - Sanders, Dora, circa 1970 (Box 7)
  - Sanders, Dora, 1970 (Box 7)
  - Sanford, Terry, 1985 (Box 7)
  - San Francisco Dance Theater, 1975 (Box 7)
  - San Francisco's Dancers Forum, 1974 (Box 7)
  - San Francisco's Dancers Workshop Company, 1970-1971 (Box 7)
  - Santana, Carlota, 1996-2002 (Box 7)
  - Schmid, Companie Schmid-Pernette, 1995 (Box 7)
  - Schmid, Companie Schmid-Pernette, 1998 (Box 7)
  - Schmidt, Beverly, 1957 (Box 7)
  - School of American Ballet, 1934 (Box 7)
  - Schulkind, Marcus, 1977-1979 (Box 7)
  - Schurman, Nona, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Seaport Mime Theatre, 1975 (Box 7)
  - Section Ten, 1974-1975 (Box 7)
  - Sephiroth Dance Theatre, 1974-1975 (Box 7)
  - Shang, Ruby, 1984 (Box 7)
  - Shankar, Uday Shankar India Culture Centre, circa 1950-1959 (Box 7)
  - Shankar, Uday Shankar India Culture Centre, 1981 (Box 7)
  - Shankar, Uday Shankar India Culture Centre, undated (Box 7)
  - Sharma, Bihari and Thambal Yaima, circa 1968 (Box 7)
  - Shawn, Ted, 1934 (Box 7)
  - Shawn, Ted, undated (Box 7)
  - Shawn, Ted newsclippings, undated (Box 7)
  - Shearer, Sybil, 1960 (Box 7)
  - Silberman, Linni, 1976 (Box 7)
  - Sircar, Ranjabati, 1999 (Box 7)
  - Sluiter, Ineke, 1962 (Box 7)
  - Smith, Bradley (photographer), circa 1950-1959 (Box 7)
  - Smith, Julia, 1964 (Box 7)
  - Soares, Janet Mansfield, 1961 (Box 7)
  - Sofian, Anahid, 1976 (Box 7)
  - Sokolow, Anna, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Sokolow, Anna Sokolow Dance Company, 1964 (Box 7)
  - Sokolow, Anna, 2000 (Box 7)
  - Sokolow, Anna, undated (Box 7)
  - Sokolow, Anna, undated (Box 7)
  - Solo Dance Theatre, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Solomons, Gus (Solomons Company), 1972 (Box 7)
  - Solomons, Jr., Gus, 1973 (Box 7)
  - Solov, Zachary Solov Ballet Ensemble, 1961 (Box 7)
  - Spiegel, Laurie, 1975 (Box 7)
  - St. Denis, Ruth, 1952-1953 (Box 7)
  - St. Denis, Ruth, 1956 (Box 7)
  - St. Denis, Ruth, 1960 (Box 7)
  - St. Denis, Ruth, undated (Box 7)
  - Stephen, Edith, 1961-1962 (Box 7)
  - Stephen, Edith Stephen Dance Theatre, 1967 (Box 7)
  - Streb, Elizabeth Streb Ringside, Inc., 1986-1998 (Box 7)
  - Sturman, Rivka, circa 1968 (Box 7)
  - Surplus Dance Theater, 1964 (Box 7)
  - Tachibana, Sahomi, 1978 (Box 7)
  - Taliaferro, Clay, 1972 (Box 7)
  - Tamiris, Helen, 1959 (Box 7)
  - Tamiris-Nagrin Dance Company, 1964 (Box 7)
  - Tamiris, Helen, undated (Box 7)
  - Tanner, Virginia, circa 1960 (Box 7)
  - Tanner, Virginia, 1975 (Box 7)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1962 (Box 7)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1964-1966 (Box 7)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1964-1967 (Box 7)
  - Taylor, Paul, 1965-1969 (Box 7)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1971 (Box 7)
  - Taylor, Paul, circa 1971 (Box 7)
  - Taylor, Paul, 1974-1976 (Box 7)
  - Taylor, Paul, 1982-1988 (Box 7)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, circa 1989 (Box 7)
  - Taylor, Paul, 1990 (Box 7)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1993 (Box 7)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1995 (Box 7)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 1998-1999 (Box 7)
  - Taylor, Paul Taylor Dance Company, 2000 (Box 7)
  - Taylor 2, undated (Box 7)
  - Terry, Walter, circa 1968 (Box 7)
  - Tetley, Glen, 1966 (Box 7)
  - Tharp, Twyla, circa 1970-1972 (Box 7)
  - Tharp, Twyla Tharp and Dance Company, circa 1967 (Box 7)
  - Tharp, Twyla Tharp and Dancers, 1970 (Box 7)
  - Tharp, Twyla Tharp Dances and Dancers, 1974 (Box 7)
  - Tharp, Twyla Tharp Dance Foundation Inc., 1977 (Box 7)
  - Tharp, Twyla, 1999 (Box 7)
  - Tharp, Twyla, 2000 (Box 7)
  - Theatre Ballet of San Francisco, 1976 (Box 7)
  - Theatre de la Danse, 1934 (Box 7)
  - Thomas, Ted, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Tiffany, Mary, 1952 (Box 7)
  - Traguth, Fred, 1966 (Box 7)
  - Van Acker, Christiane and Michael Podolski, 1970 (Box 7)
  - Van Dijk, Anouk, 2001 (Box 7)
  - Varone, Doug, 2000 (Box 7)
  - Ventura Dance Company, 2002 (Box 7)
  - Verdy, Violette, 1975 (Box 7)
  - Vernon, Charlie, 1982 (Box 7)
  - Viana, Luis, 1994 (Box 7)
  - Vianna, Klauss, 1974 (Box 7)
  - Villella, Edward, 1974 (Box 7)
  - Viswanathan, Lakshmi, 1974 (Box 7)
  - Vivekanandan, Ranga, 1978 (Box 7)
  - Waring, James, 1973 (Box 7)
  - Waring, James, 1975 (Box 7)
  - Washington, Lula Washington's Los Angeles Contemporary Dance Theatre, 1994 (Box 7)
  - Watson, Gwendolyn, 1969 (Box 7)
  - Weidman, Charles, circa 1936 (Box 7)
  - Weidman, Charles, 1954 (Box 7)
  - Weidman, Charles, 1960 (Box 7)
  - Weidman, Charles Weidman and His Theatre Dance Company, 1964 (Box 7)
  - Weidman, Charles, 1970, 1972 (Box 7)
  - Weidman, Charles Weidman Dance Foundation, 1992 (Box 7)
  - Weidman, Charles, undated (Box 7)
  - Widman, Anneliese, 1962 (Box 7)
  - Wiener, Hans Wiener and Erika Thimey, undated (Box 7)
  - Wiener, Nina Wiener and Dancers, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Wigman, Mary, 1938-1939 (Box 7)
  - Wigman, Mary, 1951 (Box 7)
  - Wigman, Mary, 1956 (Box 7)
  - Williamson, Liz, 1970 (Box 7)
  - Wilson, Robert, 1974 (Box 7)
  - Windwitches, 1988 (Box 7)
  - Winslow, Miriam, undated (Box 7)
  - Winter, Ethel Winter Dance Company, 1964 (Box 7)
  - Wodynski, Jan Wodynski Dance Company, 1975 (Box 7)
  - Wolenski, Chester, undated (Box 7)
  - Wyman, Anna Wyman Dance Theatre, 1974 (Box 7)
  - Yearby, Marlies, 1997 (Box 7)
  - Yonei, Sumie Yonei and Dancers, 1995 (Box 7)
  - York String Quartet, 1964 (Box 7)
  - Yuriko, 1955 (Box 7)
  - Yuriko, 1964-1965 (Box 7)
  - Zivili, 1978 (Box 7)